Guide to the New-York Historical Society Library Department Records 1815-2018 NYHS-RG 21
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Collection Descriptions & Inventories, 1815?-2003; 27.29 Linear feet in 46 boxes of various sizes and 3 shelved volumes
  - Subseries I.A. Descriptions Prepared by N-YHS, 1815?-2003; 25.83 Linear feet
    - Rare Book Inventory (2 folders), 1992 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 1-2)
    - Rare Book Bibliographical Information (5 folders), 1992 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 3-7)
    - Regional American Cataloging Project (3 folders), 1992 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 3-5)
    - Great Collections Microfilming Project II, 1992? (Offsite-box 15, Folder 6)
    - Library Inventory Project. Documentation & Procedures, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 7)
    - Early U.S. Government Documents Inventory Project, 1984, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 8)
    - Fast-Cat Items List, 1989 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 9)
    - Fast-Cat Items List, 1990s? (Offsite-box 15, Folder 10)
      Includes list of materials and their location on the 5th floor.
    - Map Cataloging Project I (NEH). Maps & Charts, circa 1850? (Offsite-box 28, Folder 1)
      Includes a 19th century inventory of maps in the N-YHS library.
    - Map Cataloging Project I (NEH). Early Research Notes (9 of 36 folders). A-G, circa 1800s-1920s (Offsite-box 28, Folder 2-10)
      The set of folders in this and the following boxes were noted as "early research notes" and appear to have been inventories from the late 1800s to early 1900s that were used as sources by the NEH map cataloging project staff.
    - Map Cataloging Project I (NEH). Early Research Notes (10 of 36 folders). H-Q, circa 1800s-1920s (Offsite-box 29, Folder 1-10)
    - Map Cataloging Project I (NEH). Early Research Notes (8 of 36 folders). New York City, circa 1800s-1920s, 1989 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 1-8)
    - Map Cataloging Project I (NEH). Early Research Notes (9 of 36 folders). R-Z, circa 1800s-1920s (Offsite-box 31, Folder 1-9)
    - Map Cataloging Project I (NEH). Reference Sources & Administration (17 of 69 folders), 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 1-17)
      This box and the following includes various map inventories and other reference material relevant to the N-YHS collection and project. Also includes project statistics, activity reports, grant information, and other administrative material.
    - Map Cataloging Project I (NEH). Reference Sources & Administration (23 of 69 folders), 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 1-23)
    - Map Cataloging Project I (NEH). Reference Sources & Administration (29 of 69 folders), 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 1-29)
    - Map Cataloging Project I (NEH). Survey Sheets (1 of 2 boxes), 1989-1992 (Box 35, Folder 1-11)
      These two boxes of survey sheets were boxed for off-site storage.
    - Map Cataloging Project I (NEH). Survey Sheets (2 of 2 boxes), 1989-1992 (Box 36, Folder 1-12)
    - Map Cataloging Project II (NEH). Reference Sources & Administration (17 of 34 folders), 1992-1994 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 1-17)
    - Map Cataloging Project II (NEH). Reference Sources & Administration (17 of 34 folders), 1992-1994 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 1-17)
    - Map Cataloging Project II (NEH). Preservation/Inventory Forms (3 folders), 1992-1994 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 18-20)
      Includes rolled maps and map cases H-L.
    - Map Cataloging Project II (NEH). Preservation/Inventory Forms (3 folders), 1992 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 1-3)
      Includes map case P.
    - Map Cataloging Project II (NEH). Preservation/Inventory Forms (1 of 4 boxes). #1-2699, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 1-17)
    - Map Cataloging Project II (NEH). Preservation/Inventory Forms (2 of 4 boxes). #2700-5699, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 1-15)
    - Map Cataloging Project II (NEH). Preservation/Inventory Forms (3 of 4 boxes). #5700-8499, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 1-14)
    - Map Cataloging Project II (NEH). Preservation/Inventory Forms (4 of 4 boxes). #8500-11143, Erskine-DeWitt Maps, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 1-17)
    - Manuscripts Cataloging Project (29 folders), 1998-2001 (Offsite-box 44, Folder 1-29)
      Includes progress reports, monthly production statistics, draft catalog records, and other production-related documents in connection with the Mellon-funded N-YHS/NYU project to catalog manuscript holdings.
    - Family Bible Inventory, 1998 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 10)
    - Reference Guides, 2001 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 11)
      Includes guides to research in American Revolution, military history, architecture, and newspapers.
  - Subseries I.B. Descriptions Prepared Outside N-YHS, 1881-1976; 1.46 Linear feet
    The subseries is arranged in chronological order.
    The subseries includes inventories and other material describing the content of particular collections held by N-YHS that were prepared by the original creator of the collection, donor, auction house, or other party outside of N-YHS. Four manuscript form inventories are currently in the subseries, primarily concerning the collection of Randall J. Le Boeuf, Jr. The subseries also holds at least some auction catalogues that included sales of N-YHS duplicate and other holdings from the 1940s-1960s. The container list includes reference to the specific inventories held.
    - Alphabetical List of Books from the Executors of Stephen Whitney Phoenix Estate, 1881 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - "Catalogue and Description of American Revolutionary Diaries", 1922 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      Includes William S. Thomas's manuscript version of this catalogue, the entries of which were published over several installments of the N-YHS Bulletin, beginning with the April 1922 issue. Much of the preparatory work for the entries was done by Thomas at N-YHS and many or most of the entries include N-YHS holdings, though there are non-N-YHS references as well.
    - W. Johnson Quinn Collection. New York Hotels, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Auction Catalogue. Parke-Bernet, Sale 540 (4 copies, some marked), 1944 March 13 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 1)
    - Auction Catalogue. Parke-Bernet, Sale 569 (3 copies), 1944 May 15 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 2)
    - Auction Catalogue. American Book Auction, Sale 89 (marked), 1946 April 26 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 3)
    - Auction Catalogue. Parke-Bernet, Sale 777 (3 copies, some marked), 1946 May 16 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 4)
    - Auction Catalogue. Parke-Bernet, Sale 784 (marked), 1946 September 18-21 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 5)
    - Auction Catalogue. American Book Auction, Sale 137 (marked), 1948 November 19 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 6)
    - Spanish-American War Collection, circa 1950 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      Includes an inventory of the Lathrop Colgate Harper Spanish-American War Collection distributed by Harper's estate, and an earlier version referring to the Daniel C. Edgar Collection of the Spanish-American War apparently prepared by Harper in his lifetime.
    - Auction Catalogue. American Book Auction, Sale 192 (marked), 1952 January 25 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 7)
    - Auction Catalogue. American Book Auction, Sale 197 (2 copies, marked), 1952 April 25 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 8)
    - Auction Catalogue. Parke-Bernet, Sale 1432 (marked), 1953 April 21 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 9)
    - Auction Catalogue. American Book Auction, Sale 223 (marked), 1953 November 20 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 10)
    - Auction Catalogue. Parke-Bernet, Sale 2095 (marked), 1962 March 17 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 11)
    - Auction Catalogue. American Book Auction, Sale 377 (2 copies, one marked), 1964 April 10 (Offsite-box 66, Folder 12)
    - Randall J. Le Boeuf, Jr. Catalogue. Volume IA. Autograph Material, circa 1976 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 1)
    - Randall J. Le Boeuf, Jr. Catalogue. Volume I. Robert Fulton Collection. Books, Pamphlets, & Newspapers, circa 1976 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 2)
    - Randall J. Le Boeuf, Jr. Catalogue. Volume II. Robert Fulton Collection. Books, Pamphlets, & Newspapers, circa 1976 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 3)
    - Randall J. Le Boeuf, Jr. Collection Bookplates, Undated (Offsite-box 26, Folder 4)
    - Le Boeuf's Typescript "The Origin of My Robert Fulton Collection", 1970 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 5)
    - Le Boeuf Catalogue Pages & Correspondence (6 folders), 1976 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 1-6)
      Includes prints, engravings, lithographs, glass, and other objects.
    - Le Boeuf Catalogue. Photocopy with annotations (5 folders), circa 1976 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 6-11)
    - Louis Durr Collection Catalogue (2 volumes), annotated by John A. Weeks, 1882 (Offsite-box 360)
- Series II. Acquisition Records, 1962-2001; 11.25 Linear feet
  The series includes correspondence concerning acknowledgements of donations accepted, offers of items for purchase or donation, and declined offers. These relate principally to the period 1976 to 2001, though there are some records for 1964-1975. Appraisals and related inventories for many of these donations are included through about 1986. Slips of paper with summary information by donor for the 1960s-1993 are in the series, as are a small number of acquisition related logs and system print-outs. The series also includes some records of library purchases, including purchases from 1979-1982 from Baker & Taylor, Gale Research, Heckman Bindery, university presses, subscription services, microfilm vendors, bookshops, publishers, and others.
  This series includes those acquisition records found as standalone files during processing of the archive in 2016. References to acquisitions can also be found in the administrative files described in other series of this record group.
  The acquisition files are arranged in chronological order. Some files that include documents from a wide date range, such as files of pending donations and of multiple donations by individual over time, are placed at the latest date found in the file. At the end of the principal acquisition files are found boxes of donor slips, which include summary donation information, and copies of bills for library purchases.
  - Acquisitions, Donations, Acknowledgements, 1964-1969 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Streeter, Thomas R., 1964 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Includes lists of Streeter's donations from 1947-1964.
  - Appraisals, 1962-1969 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Acquisitions, Donations, Acknowledgements, 1970-1975 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Appraisals (6 folders), 1970-1975 (Box 45, Folder 5-10)
    Includes the extensive inventory of the collection of Edith McC. Heaphy, Ethel McC. Scott, and John G. McCullough.
  - Goelet, Robert G., 1971-1977, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Acquisitions, Donations, Acknowledgements, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Appraisals, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Acquisitions, Donations, Acknowledgements, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Appraisals, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Acquisitions, Donations, Acknowledgements, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Acquisitions, Donations, Acknowledgements (2 folders), 1979 (Box 46, Folder 6-7)
  - Appraisals, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Orders, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Proposed Acquisitions (Offers), 1976-1979 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Declined Offers, 1975-1979 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Acquisitions, Donations, Acknowledgements, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Appraisals, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Declined Offers, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Maritime Association of the Port of New York, 1978-1980 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Acquisitions, Donations, Acknowledgements (3 folders), 1981 (Box 47, Folder 5-7)
  - Appraisals, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Declined Offers, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Acquisitions, Donations, Acknowledgements (3 folders), 1982 (Box 48, Folder 1-3)
  - Appraisals, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Proposed Acquisitions (Offers), 1980-1982 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Declined Offers, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Donald Clark Bequest, 1981-1983 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Acquisitions, Donations, Acknowledgements (2 folders), 1983 (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
  - Appraisals, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Proposed Acquisitions (Offers), 1983 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Declined Offers, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Alland, Alexander (Bracklow Photographs), 1983 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Greenberg, Morris/Stanley, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Schwartz, Robert R., 1979-1983 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Orders, 1980-1983 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Serials, 1980-1985 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Acquisitions, Donations, Acknowledgements (4 folders), 1984 (Box 50, Folder 1-4)
  - Proposed Acquisitions (Offers), 1984 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Acquisition Procedures and Statistics (2 folders), 1984 (Box 50, Folder 6-7)
  - Acquisitions, Donations, Acknowledgements (2 folders), 1985 (Box 50, Folder 8-9)
  - Proposed Acquisitions (Offers), 1984-1985 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Orders, 1984-1985 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Kemble, William, 1983-1986 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Acquisitions, Donations, Acknowledgements (2 folders), 1986 (Box 51, Folder 1-2)
  - Proposed Acquisitions (Offers), 1986 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Declined Offers, 1984-1986 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Appraisals, 1984-1986 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Acquisitions, Donations, Acknowledgements (4 folders), 1987 (Box 51, Folder 6-9)
  - Additions to the Manuscript Collection Log, 1986-1988 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Acquisitions, Donations, Acknowledgements (2 folders), 1988 (Box 52, Folder 1-2)
  - Acquisitions, Donations, Acknowledgements, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Steinway, Henry Z., 1986-1989 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Acquisitions, Donations, Acknowledgements (2 folders), 1990 (Box 52, Folder 5-6)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, 1987-1990 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Schneck, Jerome, 1985-1990 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Acquisitions, Donations, Acknowledgements (2 folders), 1991 (Box 53, Folder 1-2)
  - Alpern, Andrew, 1976-1991 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Brooklyn Bureau of Community Service, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Wyle, D. (Ensko Collection), 1991 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Acquisitions, Donations, Acknowledgements (2 folders), 1991-1992 (Box 53, Folder 6-7)
  - Whitlock, Bache McE., 1987-1992 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Wheeler, Charles B., 1986-1992 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Donors. Miscellaneous, 1988-1992 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Acquisition Records (Print-outs, from Binder) (3 folders), 1991-1992 (Box 54, Folder 1-3)
  - Acquisition Records (Print-outs, from Binder) (4 folders), 1992 (Box 54, Folder 4-7)
  - New Acquisitions (2 folders), 1991 July-1992 March (Box 54, Folder 8-9)
  - Miscellaneous Acquisitions-Related Notes, 1988-1992 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Donations FY1993, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Donations Accepted & Rejected FY1994, 1993-1994 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Donations Pending FY1994, 1987, 1994, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    Includes a medallion with religious imagery and Cyrillic (?) characters.
  - Donation Files FY1995 (4 folders), 1994-1995 (Box 55, Folder 4-7)
  - Donation Files FY1996 (1 of 4 folders) (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Donation Files FY1996 (3 of 4 folders), 1995-1996 (Box 56, Folder 1-3)
  - Donation Files FY1997 (8 folders), 1996-1997 (Box 56, Folder 4-11)
  - Donation Files FY1998 (1 of 8 folders) (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Donation Files FY1998 (7 of 8 folders), 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 1-7)
  - Donation Files FY1999 (6 of 11 folders), 1998-1999 (Box 57, Folder 8-13)
  - Donation Files FY1999 (5 of 11 folders), 1998-1999 (Box 58, Folder 1-5)
  - Unsolicited Donations, 1995-1999 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Donation Files FY2000 (2 of 7 folders), 1999-2000 (Box 58, Folder 7-8)
  - Donation Files FY2000 (5 of 7 folders), 1999-2000 (Box 59, Folder 1-5)
  - Donation Files FY2001 (1 of 6 folders), 1999-2001 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Donation Files FY2001 (6 of 7 folders), 2000-2001 (Box 60, Folder 1-6)
  - Donation Files FY2001. Print Room (4 folders), 2000-2001 (Box 60, Folder 7-10)
  - Donor Slips. A-K, 1960s-1979 (Box 61, Cards -)
  - Donor Slips. L-Z, 1960s-1979 (Box 62, Cards -)
  - Donor Slips, 1978, 1980 (Box 63, Cards -)
  - Donor Slips. A-M, 1980-1989 (Box 63, Cards -)
  - Donor Slips. N-Z, 1980-1989 (Box 64, Cards -)
  - Donor Slips. A-Z, 1990-1993 (Box 64, Cards unknown container)
  - Library Purchases (11 folders), 1979-1982 (Offsite-box 65, Folder 1-11)
  - Newspapers (14 folders), 1972-circa 2003 (Offsite-box 358)
    These are files transfered to the Archives in 2021 by longtime librarian Marian Touba. They include information on newspaper acquisition, with some deaccessioning information.
- Series III. General Office Files, 1959-2009 (bulk 1980s-2002); 27.17 Linear feet
  The series is arranged with what appears to be five relatively well-defined original sets of correspondence and subject files first, followed by various miscellaneous administrative and topical files. The five well-defined sets are identified in the container list by the prefixes
  The General Office Files appear to have been maintained over time by the administrative assistants to the Library Director, including Mary Nathanson, Xenia Zielyk, Grace Hernandez, Patricia Contino, Sarah Grossman and others, though other files were likely mixed into these over time. Accordingly, the files hold a combination of management-level material (e.g., budgets and expense information, grants and grant proposals, annual or other management progress reports, activity statistics, staff memos, correspondence, general exhibition planning, fellowship proposals, donations, and acquisitions) as well as routine transactional documents (e.g., invoices for Baker & Taylor, Readmore, Blackwell, RLG/RLIN and other library purchases and subscriptions).
  There is considerable overlap in the subject matter of this series and the next, Series III. Librarian and Curatorial Files. There likely is no sharp distinction between them, but generally the content of the files in Series III seems more attributable to particular leaders in the library, while these general files seem to have a more varied provenance, including miscellaneous files added to the series by archivists over time.
  - Correspondence Files. Subjects. A-P (30 of 70 folders), circa 1986-1993 (Offsite-box 67, Folder 1-30)
    This set of folders includes correspondence with outside parties and internal memos on a wide variety of matters, including offers of donations, purchase offers, requests for information, proposals for programs, compliments and complaints from the public, staff meeting notes, public remarks by Jean Ashton, professional matters, and more. Subject files are arranged by either subject or institutional addressee; individual files are arranged by a particular person's name. Librarians James Mooney and Jean Ashton appear to be the principal N-YHS correspondents.
  - Correspondence Files. Subjects. P-Z (16 of 70 folders), circa 1986-1993 (Offsite-box 68, Folder 1-16)
    Includes files on the publication of the papers resulting from a series of conferences hosted by N-YHS in the 1980s.
  - Correspondence Files. Individuals. A-Z (24 of 70 folders ), circa 1986-1993 (Offsite-box 69, Folder 1-24)
  - Subject Files. A-D (51 of 237 folders), circa 1986-1997 (Offsite-box 70, Folder 1-51)
    Topics include, among others, accessioning procedures; acquisitions, especially Livingston Papers (including inventory); Advisory Committee ("AC" on labels); appraisals; attorney general; Baker & Taylor; buildings & construction; collections management and descriptions/profiles of the collections; conference "Power of the Press"; deeds of gift (originals); directory listings; and disaster plan.
  - Subject Files. E-F (37 of 237 folders), circa 1986-1997 (Offsite-box 71, Folder 1-37)
    The bulk of the box includes exhibition files, including general files of proposals, schedules, descriptions, etc. These principally concern the library/reading room exhibitions, but also include other N-YHS exhibitions. Specific matters include, among others, the Spanish-American War Project, map collection, Markers of Change, Letters From a War, McLoughlin woodcuts, Early New York Printing (includes an 1981 inventory of paper money in N-YHS's collection), Rufus King, and unique slavery material. The rest of the box includes four folders of fiscal crisis letters, clippings, and staff memos.
  - Subject Files. F-L (40 of 237 folders), circa 1986-1997 (Offsite-box 72, Folder 1-40)
    Topics include, among others, fundraising, gifts/exchanges (includes index cards and other documents recording exchanges with other institutions in 1979-1983), Harper Fund, income from endowments/restricted funds, IRLA, and library matters (organization charts, conservation lab, collections management, acquisitions policy, refurbishing, staff meeting notes, and Library Night labels.
  - Subject Files. L-O (33 of 237 folders), circa 1986-1997 (Offsite-box 73, Folder 1-33)
    Topics include, among others, library loans, Luce Center planning (including vendor software proposals), McLoughlin blocks (see also the folders for exhibitions above), manuscript room matters, microfilm readers, lists of new titles/acquisitions in the library, N-YHS matters (website, bibliography, capital budget for 1993-94, report to the state on its financial stabilization plans), newspaper collections, Old Print Shop, Zenger letter.
  - Subject Files. O-R (36 of 237 folders), circa 1986-1997 (Offsite-box 74, Folder 1-36)
    Topics include, among others, OPAC, personnel (job descriptions, postings, policies, staff lists), planning, publishing/royalty statements, appraisals for publishing-related donations, quiz show filming in library, and RLG/RLIN projects, invoices, etc.
  - Subject Files. R-Z (40 of 237 folders), circa 1986-1997 (Offsite-box 75, Folder 1-40)
    Topics include, among others, RLG/RLIN, security, library signage, space planning, stack 15 relocation, technical services/cataloging, and a collective bargaining agreement. The box also holds many folders concerning library statistics for 1988-1998 (reading room, manuscripts, Print Room, with some gaps).
  - General Files. FY1991-1992 (16 of 25 folders), 1988-1992 (Offsite-box 77, Folder 1-16)
    Includes budget files for FY1989 and 1990 as well as 1991 and 1992.
  - General Files. FY1991-1992 (9 of 25 folders), 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 78, Folder 1-9)
    Includes, among other topics, a report on duplicates in the caricature collection, a bibliography of N-YHS library holdings bearing on Native American history, collections profiles, and a file for the proposed exhibition Patrons, Collectors & Collections.
  - General Files. FY1993 (9 folders), 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 79, Folder 1-9)
  - General Files. FY1994 (4 of 22 folders), 1993-1994 (Offsite-box 79, Folder 10-13)
  - General Files. FY1994 (18 of 22 folders), 1993-1996 (Offsite-box 80, Folder 1-22)
    Includes documents related to staffing plans, N-YHS's discussions with New York University and a file of calendars and other documents related to public programs from 1993-1996.
  - General Files. FY1995 (5 of 24 folders), 1994-1995 (Offsite-box 80, Folder 23-27)
  - General Files. FY1995 (19 of 24 folders), 1994-1995 (Offsite-box 81, Folder 1-19)
    Includes, among other topics, reading room statistics and working papers of a survey of other libraries regarding their admission and service fees.
  - General Files. FY1996 (12 of 22 folders), 1995-1996 (Offsite-box 82, Folder 1-12)
  - General Files. FY1996 (10 of 22 folders), 1995-1996 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 1-10)
  - General Files. FY1997 (13 of 25 folders), 1996-1997 (Offsite-box 83, Folder 11-23)
  - General Files. FY1997 (12 of 25 folders), 1996-1997 (Offsite-box 84, Folder 1-12)
    Includes, among other topics, text for labels to exhibition Love Letters, a report on a steam leak in the stacks, a middle school program called Shadow Day, and a copy of the agreement between N-YHS and New York University for library services.
  - General Files. FY1998 (15 of 20 folders), 1997-1998 (Offsite-box 84, Folder 13-27)
    Includes, among other topics, correspondence concerning the Fabres collection.
  - General Files. FY1998 (5 of 20 folders), 1997-1998 (Offsite-box 85, Folder 1-5)